Altogether you've scored
over 400 points!
Anyone who hurt my students -
no matter who - I won't forgive!
Isn't today the test?
You'll be fired because of me.
You know, this is more important
than some test.
Because I'm your homeroom
teacher.
Thank you, Sensei!
English Subtitles by
STUDIO NEW MEDIA
Subtitles Edited and Timed by
SCHWEFELHEXAFLUORID
D-ADDICTS
www.d-addicts.com
Come on, Onizuka-sensei.
- Sensei!
- Onizuka-sensei!
No!
Director...
It was my fault.
When Murai-kun telephoned,
I should have let him talk
to Onizuka-sensei.
It'll be okay.
It'll take more than this
to kill a man like him.
Because you see, he's the Great
Teacher Onizuka.
This is no time to be crying.
The real battle starts now,
for Onizuka, and ourselves.
But...
But I don't know what to do.
Then why don't you
become GTF too?
The Great Teacher Fuyutsuki.
So, you think Onitchi's okay?
There's no need to worry,
Fuyutsuki just said
over the phone,
his life's not in danger.
But I can't forgive that Tôdô,
to stab him in the back!
And to do that to Miyabi to just
pass time was terrible!
Hey! Hey! Who's that?
Who the heck is that?
- Looks like someone important.
- Who is he?
Finally!
With this, it's for certain that
Onizuka will be fired.
You did it, Teshigawara-sensei!
- It was a complete success!
- What a joyous day!
Oh! Tôdô-san!
It's been a while...
Oh, Teshigawara-kun, so this
is where you're working.
Yes.
Oh, so why are you here today?
Well, I have something
important to discuss.
It's Tôdô-san,
my father's supervisor.
- At the Ministry of Education?
- He's this terms vice-president.
What?
I'm head teacher Uchiyamada.
- Is the principal here?
- Oh, well...
due to various circumstances,
the academy's director
is currently acting as principal.
I see, so that's why this academy
has so many problems.
Excuse me?
My son, who means more
than life itself to me,
was seriously injured by one
of your violent teachers.
That's not all.
That man, Onizuka, also did
terrible harm to ten
- of his good friends!
- What?!
This goes beyond corporal
punishment to attempted murder!
How does Seirin Academy intend
to take responsibility for this?
It will be dealt with immediately.
- I'll tell you this.
- Yes?
With this situation, this academy's
accreditation as a place
of education may be judged
inappropriate
by the Ministry of Education.
Are you alright, Onizuka-sensei?
- The test.
- What?
Ask Uchiyamada if I can take
the test over...
No you don't! You have to rest!
I'm okay, this is nothing!
Stop it and just trust me!
I told you before, didn't I?
That I wouldn't let them fire you.
A woman doesn't go back
on her word.
Leave the school to me.
Don't do anything reckless,
just concentrate on getting better.
Okay? Do you understand?
Yes.
Would you like some water?
I was just reminded
of something.
What's that?
Well, you see,
when I was in elementary school,
when my homeroom teacher
really chewed me out.
Murai, you okay?
I'm being discharged already.
Aw man, you've got it easy!
Stop it, you have to lay down.
Sensei, Tôdô's dad came
marching into school
and raised a major ruckus.
But they were the ones who
were wrong, right?
But even if we told them that,
would they believe us?
It'll be alright, if I talk to my mom,
she can do something.
I'll watch out for you, Sensei.
Because...
you are my homeroom teacher,
you're the only one.
Got it!
We have to fire Onizuka
immediately!
Besides, he got a zero
on the test.
I don't think Tôdô-san will be
satisfied with just that.
What do you mean?
What I'm saying is that he'll want
the school to take responsibility
for having such a violent teacher.
It was only for two months,
but it is true that he was
part of our staff.
Then how about this?
How about if we erase all
proof that that man
- was ever at our academy?
- There's no way!
You wouldn't be able to get
all the students
and parents to agree to that!
Then, Onizuka has a split
personality and he doesn't
remember a thing about
when he got violent.
Hakamada-sensei, will you
please be quiet!
- What should we do?
- Then, how about this?
Since Onizuka was an uncertified
teacher, he had agreed that
if he did not score over 400
on the test, he would quit.
However, when it came
to the test he scored a zero.
That means from the day
of that test,
he was no longer a teacher
at this academy.
Since he was no longer
a teacher here,
the academy has no
responsibility.
That's good! Let's go with that!
Good thinking,
Teshigawara-sensei!
I figured that was the only way.
- Excuse me.
- What is it?
I really think this is a forced
explanation.
It's like trying to fill
empty space.
We don't have time for this!
This is first crisis this academy
has faced since I started.
The important thing is to protect
the academy's image!
That's right,
what are you thinking?
I'm sorry.
What bullshit, they're just
protecting themselves.
That Uchiyamada wants
to become principal,
so he's desperate.
But when it comes down to it,
it's really the director's fault.
To accept Onizuka under
special conditions
was a mistake in the first place.
In any case, the academy will
need to send expressions
of concern to Tôdô-san
and the parents
of the injured Jinnan students.
That is the best course
of action for now.
I would like everyone to be
careful not to speak to the media.
- Yes.
- I think this attitude is all wrong!
Fuyutsuki-sensei, you again?
They were the ones who
were really wrong!
If Tôdô-san's son hadn't done
what he did to hurt Aizawa Miyabi.
So it was okay to beat high
school students half to death?
But if Onizuka-sensei
hadn't helped,
something even worse may have
happened to Aizawa Miyabi.
Onizuka-sensei was only trying
to protect his own students.
Of course, I think he
owes an apology
for injuring those students.
But beyond that, he hasn't done
anything unjustified or wrong,
and I intend to fight for that!
You aren't in a position
of responsibility,
so you can say such
idealistic things.
But this is just making him
a sacrificial lamb!
I think you're going too far,
Fuyutsuki-sensei.
- Think of our position!
- What do you expect us to do?
No matter what happens,
I will fight!
I wonder if it's okay for her
to argue that much with
Uchiyamada.
There's no one else
supporting her.
We can't count on that old fart.
- It'll be okay.
- What do you mean?
Miyabi's trying to her mother
to convince the school
to keep Onizuka.
There's nothing to worry
about then.
Yeah, that Uchiyamada can't
stand up to the PTA president.
I wonder if it'll be that easy...
Please, Mama!
If Onizuka wasn't there,
I don't know what would
have happened to me.
Because of him, I finally realized
how stupid I was being.
Mama, you're the only one
I can count on.
So, please!
Alright.
Really?
I will meet with the head
teacher immediately
- and voice my objection.
- Thank you!
If Uchiyamada argues,
then you can scare him
and say you'll bring it up
in your next talk.
I know.
Leave it up to your mama.
Hello, Aizawa residence.
It's been a while, Aizawa-sensei.
Oh, Tôdô-san!
How are you?
Yes, well, there was something
I wanted to ask of you.
Yes?
Yes.
What?
Aw! It's no visitors!
- What now?
- Go in! Go in!
Let's go in!
Aw! Ya got me!
- Nuts!
- Straight!
Sheeet! Not again!
Let's play something else!
You sure you're not cheating?
Thanks for the business!
Oh, it's you guys.
Onitchi! You okay?
You're supposed to be resting!
Stupid! Of course I'm fine!
But don't you have a broken rib?
Yeah, you know if that stab
wound was just a little off,
it could have been fatal!
As a teacher, I can't die
on my students!
- Onitchi, for you.
- Thanks!
Here, from me too. Some pornos.
- Oh thanks!
- Here, Sensei!
Wow, so much!
You know, we thought
there's no way
a guy like him could
be a teacher.
- Yeah, we never figured!
- He's the only fool who could.
Yeah, the other night he told
such a weak story.
The one about
the dreadful shiûmai,
the ones that were stuck
to the cover, you know?
- Totally stale, wasn't it?
- It was!
But the one about the baby
in the coin locker
was scary, wasn't it?
The one, "It's you!"
That one, that's one
of my originals.
- I told him that one.
- What? Really?
You got any others?
Okay then, this is the one
about the hospital
- that you can never leave.
- Oh! Sounds scary!
What do you think you
are doing?
The hospital is not a playground,
how many times do
I have to tell you!
- Yes, ma'am!
- For heaven sake!
And you too,
didn't you see that it's
"no visitors"?
- We're sorry.
- Alright.
- Eikichi!
- Yes?
Touch my butt again,
and you'll get an injection
that'll hurt like you
wouldn't believe.
- Yes.
- Students from your class?
- Oh?
You must have it rough,
having him for a homeroom
teacher.
That's right!
You wouldn't believe
how we suffer!
Hey, what's that?!
Hey, Miyabi!
- Sensei, for you.
- Thank you.
Forgive me.
- I've brought you some clothes.
- Thanks.
Oh, thank you for everything.
- Oh yes, he's quite a handful.
- Here, T-shirts.
- Thanks.
- Oh!
- Your girlfriend?
- That's right.
- No, I'm not!
- She is.
No, I'm not!
I teach at the same school,
my name is Fuyutsuki.
Oh, I'm the nurse
in charge of him.
I am not!
- Please take it easy, okay?
- Yes.
I'm going to make you realize
your situation, Onizuka-sensei.
With this, the public will
thoroughly investigate you.
IN THE CASE OF THE CHILDREN
BEAT NEARLY TO DEATH
THE TRUTH BEHIND
THE INCIDENT WAS HIDDEN.
Morning.
- So how'd they do?
- They lost.
- Again?
- Yes, 3 to 0.
What are they doing.
- The me-me-me...
- What is it?
Sir!
The me-me-me...
- What are you guys doing?
- The me-me...
It's the media!
What are we going to do?
We have to get rid
of them, quickly!
Yes!
What kind of teacher is he?
How is this incident affecting
the students?
Well, Head Teacher?
Aren't you in charge here?
At this point, we have
no comment.
Isn't there a problem with
those in charge?
No, well...
I can't believe it!
To do that to innocent children!
And on top of that, he was a high
school teacher?
What is this world coming to?
Director, we must quickly release
a statement that Onizuka
has nothing to do with
our academy.
This is a crisis for this academy!
They say, after being in a pinch,
there's always a chance,
don't they?
When the children see
the academy's reputation
in the gutter, next years
enrollment will plummet.
We'll end up bankrupt!
That's right,
in baseball, it's after two outs.
It's an unrefutable fact that
Onizuka seriously injured
students from Jinnan Academy!
You can tell, just look at his eyes.
He's got the eyes of a criminal!
What? No!
They're wonderful,
the eyes of a saint.
A saint? What do you mean?
You don't understand
a thing, do you?
In any case, until he
is discharged,
we have to believe
in him and wait.
That is the attitude as educators
that we must take.
Director!
For an opinion of this incident,
we turn to education expert,
Aizawa-sensei.
We understand your daughter
is enrolled
at the school in question?
I will be clear
and to the point on this.
I do not think that that particular
teacher is at fault here.
Go for it, Mama!
I'm counting on you!
Rather, the heavier fault
lies with the school
that hired such
a dangerous teacher.
I had adamantly warned them
from before.
That a violent teacher like that
should have immediately
been excused from the school.
What are you saying?
I will now conduct a thorough
investigation into this matter.
Thank you.
Regarding this incident,
we haven't heard anything
from any representatives
from the school.
Also, it is not known
what the teacher
in question is doing right now.
- White.
- Black.
- Pink.
- Purple!
Ah! C'mon!
- Damn!
- Pay up!
Thanks again!
- Red.
- Black.
White.
Strawberry print with lacy edges?
What do you think you
are doing?
Yes, well, he's a problem
to us too.
Onizuka-sensei was never
qualified to be a teacher
- in the first place.
- Yes, yes.
Please rest assured,
he soon will not be around
and this academy will
return to normal.
We are not involved with this,
it is Onizuka-sensei's
personal affair.
I do not know.
And so, well... I'm sorry!
That's why I would
like you to listen.
Onizuka-sensei was trying
to rescue
his own student
Aizawa Miyabi...
Fuyutsuki-sensei,
I told you not to say
anything unnecessary.
But we should explain the truth
to the parents...
What are we going to do,
Head Teacher!
The calls from the parents
are endless!
And the director won't speak up.
And no matter how much we wait,
the media won't give up.
Just now, they stuck
a mike in my face
and made me out like a criminal!
I understand.
I'll grant them an interview.
Are you sure about this?
I'll tell them off!
I'll silence them once and for all!
Looks like Uchiyamada's finally
going to talk to them.
I think there's even more of them!
You know, they just
interviewed me.
Me too! Me too! I should have
spruced up some!
- It woulda been a waste.
- Shaddap!
Everyone, I'm sorry.
There's nothing for you
to apologize for, Miyabi.
But what're we going to do?
This time Onizuka'll really be fired.
In any case, all of you stay put.
Listen now, don't take a single
step out of this classroom!
No matter what the media asks,
don't answer them!
Understand? Got that?
Thank you for your patience.
I would like to start this
press conference
concerning this incident.
Why haven't you granted
an interview until now?
Yes, well...
We were still in the middle
of investigating...
That doesn't address
our concerns!
Isn't this conference a little late?
Yes, well, you see...
The teacher involved is still
hospitalized and we still...
As head teacher,
how are you going
to take responsibility for this?
This teacher's under your
supervision, isn't he?
Yes, but you see he's...
Well, we still need
to talk to him...
Have you heard?
There's piles of reporters
at Seirin Academy.
Something about some violent
teacher causing problems.
No way!
- Can I help you?
- It was you, wasn't it.
You sent a press leak
to the media.
- What are you talking about?
- Don't play innocent!
Never mind.
You're the one who stabbed
Onizuka, right?
If this gets out of hand,
I think it'll be bad for you too.
- Do you have any proof?
- Why you!
Miyabi's a witness!
Who's going to believe
what you say?
Besides, if I ask my dad, he can
fix any problem like that easily.
You smart ass!
- Why you!
- Murai!
You're smart, so you
should realize,
the one who holds power
in society wins.
But that's right, you didn't
make it into our school.
Tôdô...
- We'll tell you just one thing.
- What's that?
In order to protect Onizuka,
we will do anything.
You're smart, so you
should realize.
What we mean by anything.
Tôdô-kun, how are you doing?
- How are you feeling?
- Thanks for asking, Director.
- I'm fine now.
- I see. I'm glad.
Your father was worried too.
What an unfortunate incident,
wasn't it?
- Is something wrong?
- No, it's nothing.
We've told you already!
- Would you please stop already!
- Please, just a minute!
Please let me see Tôdô-san!
We told you, he is busy
right now!
Then I will wait as long
as it takes!
What is all the commotion?
We're so sorry.
This woman barged in,
she will be leaving now.
Please! I would like
to talk to you.
- You're being a nuisance!
- It's alright.
Please.
You may go.
You're a teacher at Seirin
Academy?
Yes, my name is Fuyutsuki.
I...
believe that your son is at fault
for this incident.
I see, and so?
I do apologize for Onizuka-
sensei using violence.
But that was because your
son was playing
a game that hurt one
of our students.
Please hold on a minute.
There is no reason my Shin'ichi
would do something like that.
Why do you say that?
Excuse me for sounding rude,
but Jinnan Academy
is a higher level than yours,
and he has been at the top ever
since his first year there.
As long as his grades are good,
then is that all that matters?
That isn't any different than
the parents at our school.
As long as their scores are good,
nothing else matters.
Have you talked to your son
about this incident?
Children may not listen to what
their parents say,
but they copy what their
parents do.
And so...
Oh my, it's exactly as you say.
My upbringing of him
was bad. I see.
Thank you for bringing this
to my attention.
However...
I think you should take a look
at your own position
and act accordingly.
Fuyutsuki-sensei.
Your own situation.
I told you, if you do anything
more unnecessary you'd be fired!
To go to Tôdô-san's home!
Do you enjoy complicating
the matter even more?
That was not my intention!
The media is so troublesome,
and the parents are so persistent.
And the director won't speak up!
We're completely exhausted!
Show us some consideration!
I just couldn't believe that Onizuka-
sensei would be fired like this.
What's with you and the director?
Why do you stand up so
much for Onizuka?
Or could it be...
that you're romantically involved?
- Of course not!
- In any case,
if you do anything
reckless again,
we'll have to consider
disciplining you too.
Do you mean I'll be fired?
If you cannot abide by
the policies of the academy,
then it cannot be helped.
What is that face?
You can give your letter
of resignation now if you like.
I...
I have not done anything wrong!
You know it causes us problems
to have someone going off.
I guess she thought she could
do something by herself.
You can't achieve anything
by yourself.
See ya!
- Oh, Sensei!
- Hello.
I've heard it's been pretty
rough at school.
Yes, the media's been
pressing us.
You know, that guy always
makes a mess!
I'm friends with a cop
in the juvenile division.
So is the police involved too?
There's going to be
an inquiry soon.
You see, they couldn't
question him until now.
So what's going to happen?
Well, he'll probably be
arrested for assault.
They can't...
Don't worry, I'll do something.
Although I don't know what
a lowly patrolman like me can do.
But I'll look out for him for sure!
Well then.
How're you feeling,
Onizuka-sensei?
Yeah, well, I'm perfectly fine.
The doctor says I'm making
a miraculous recovery.
But you shouldn't strain yourself.
Yeah, but I'm bored, and I want
to go back to school soon.
- What are you reading?
- What?
Um, well... Well, you see,
I figured I could do with
a little more culture.
Oh, um...
It's not what you think!
You know, that Saejima kept
insisting on bringing them!
You're not mad?
I'm no good.
I thought I could hang in there
until you were discharged.
But I can't do a thing!
I don't know what
to do anymore.
After everything,
I can't become a GTF.
Oh geeze, seeing this
is so pitiful.
Isn't it?
It makes it look like you're trying
to hide something, Papa.
Yeah! I'm so embarrassed
I can't go
to the university tomorrow!
Papa, TV makes you look fat,
doesn't it?
You know, say what you will,
but I've been going through a lot!
So, what's going to happen
to Eikichi?
He's going to be fired, of course!
What? Why?
He's such a good man, right?
You guys don't know a thing
about Onizuka.
You're the one who doesn't
understand, Papa.
What's that?
If you really fire Eikichi,
then I'll never speak to you, ever!
- Hey, Yoshiko!
- Me too.
I'm on Eikichi-san's side too.
You too?! Wait!
Hey, wait!
Hello, Uchiyamada residence.
Hello, this is Tôdô.
Tôdô-san! What is it?
I haven't gotten a clear response,
so I've been wondering what
has been going on.
I'm so sorry!
Um, I will contact you tomorrow.
Well, the director is being so
indecisive it leaves me in a bind.
There is one way of settling this.
What is it?
If you listen, then you will quickly
become principal.
Uchiyamada-sensei.
If it's anything I can do...
This where the violent teacher,
who attacked
a student from another school,
is employed at:
Musashino Seirin Academy.
Today, an emergency meeting
of the entire school
and administration has
been called.
The disciplinary action against
that teacher will be decided.
You cannot delay any longer,
Director.
Today is the day, you will have
to face the students
and parents and explain
everything.
I understand.
In keeping the media at bay,
we would like to apologize for
all the worry we have put
the parents through.
As head teacher, I would like
to offer our findings.
All of this due to the man
Onizuka
who lacked any common sense.
I am sure everyone gathered
here is aware of this.
That man, caused problems
after problems.
Which culminated into this
latest incident.
Many times, we had asked
the director
to release Onizuka-sensei
immediately.
It fell on deaf ears.
However, this time, with all of you
and your parents,
we call for his release.
Otherwise, we feel that none
of you will be able
to return to school at ease.
And so we ask, Director,
how do you answer this?
Today...
we would like to hear something
we can believe.
It appears that a decision
is being made in the gym.
However, where is the violent
teacher in question?
We would like to hear what he
thinks of this situation.
- Hey, stop it!
- Will you stop it, we're working!
What's going on?
You... you're Onizuka-sensei,
aren't you?
Head Teacher!
First, we have an urgent
proposal.
What is it?
We understand that it was
entirely the directors idea
to hire Onizuka-sensei.
That means that the director
is the one ultimately
responsible for this incident.
That makes her even more
responsible.
In conclusion,
all the parents here,
ask for the director's dismissal.
We as teachers love this school.
In order to protect it's image,
we also concur.
Please wait!
- I'm against this!
- Me... me too!
What's going on?
- It's a putsch.
- Putsch?
They all plotted together to get
Onizuka and the director to quit.
Why those...?
Well then,
the parents and teachers
are in agreement.
Onizuka-sensei will be relieved
of his position.
And the director will
be dismissed.
Now, for the issue
of a new director.
The Ministry of Education
is currently looking
for an individual who would
show appropriate care
for our academy.
I believe we will soon be able
to introduce him to you.
With that, we will close
this assembly.
Dismissed!
Director,
thank you for your hard work.
Hold on!
Onizuka-sensei!
- Should you be here?
- I'm fine!
What's going on?
Well, you see...
Sensei!
Are you going to resort
to violence again?
Head Teacher, I have just
one question.
What's that?
Why aren't you holding classes?
I just went by the classrooms,
and there wasn't anyone there.
What's everyone doing here?
I guess you don't realize your
own situation, do you?
The only thing I'm interested
in is my students.
What?
Oh hey, everyone, listen,
I got a letter from Tomoko!
She going to be on TV!
And she was worried that
she might blunder,
so she wrote me a letter!
Alright.
Hey!
What do you think you're doing?
Well you see, pretty soon
is the class trip,
and we need to decide what
to do for the school festival.
That doesn't concern you
anymore!
Hey, Chikako, Erika!
I got my hands on some concert
tickets while I was in the hospital!
Stop it already!
Give it up already!
Noboru!
I've got some new really
scary stories!
Hey Kikuchi, you can try again,
so study hard!
Nanako!
I got you some info on fashions!
Onitchi!
Miyabi, Murai!
There's nothing in your way now.
You two should date!
- Go on back.
- Come on everyone!
Hurry up and go back.
Return to your class!
Onizuka-sensei...
The entire time he was
hospitalized,
he was thinking of his students.
He wasn't concerned or thought
anything about being fired.
And yet...
Why are you making a teacher
like that quit?
Is the image of the school
so important?
Are you all so concerned about
your own positions?
If that's the case...
Then I will quit,
from a school like this!
Will you tell him?
If he does something
like this again,
we can't guarantee the safety
of his life.
I'm sorry.
I really wish he would be more
concerned with his health.
Instead of thinking of his
students all the time.
But you know,
his school must be
a wonderful school,
if there's teacher's
like him there.
Oh! Peace has finally returned
to our academy!
This and everything is thanks
to the head teacher,
no, should I say "principal"?
Yes, well, I'm so relieved too.
My suffering is finally over.
It's terrible!
- What are you screaming about?
- Onizuka's gone now.
There isn't a single student here!
And there's still one
more term left.
Thank you for everything.
But won't they be surprised
to hear that Musashino
Seirin Academy will closed and be
absorbed into Jinnan Academy.
2016-08